

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hard-working graduate with a BS in Software Engineering from the "Institute of Management Sciences Peshawar." With one year of experience in Linux Administration, Kubernetes Administration, and proficient with Configuration Management tools. I aim to leverage my acquired academic knowledge, experience, and creative thinking to successfully fill the DevOps role at your company.

CONTACT

Mobile: +923415773905 Email: mehrab.uddin905@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mehrab

nttps://www.iinkedin.com/in/menrat uddindrnil

uddindrnil

Address: Rawalpindi, Islamabad.

LANGUAGES

- English
- Urdu
- Pashto

HOBBIES

- Book Reading
- Football
- Cooking

MEHRAB UDDIN

DEVOPS/K8S ADMINISTRATOR

WORK EXPERIENCE

MERN STACK DEVELOPER

Morosoft, 2021-present

- Front-end design
- ReactJS, NextJS, Tailwind CSS
- Implementing web design and development principles to build stable software.
- Collaborating closely with the team to support projects during all phases of delivery.
- Building websites and apps that are responsive and usable.

LINUX / KUBERNETES ADMINISTRATION

At Hazza Institute of Technology Islamabad, 2020-2021

TASKS AND RESPONSIBILITIES

- Install and Configure Linux Systems
- Perform System Maintenance
- Monitor System Performance
- Maintain System Security
- Creating cluster on-premise Cloud
- Deploying application and orchestrate
- · Creating Pods, Deployments, services, replicatset

Tools:

- Kubernetes
- Docker
- Ansible
- Git
- AWS Practitioner

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

INSTITUTE OF MANAGMENT SCIENCES PESHAWAR BS SOFTWARE ENGINEERING. 2015-2019

VECTOR SCHOOL & COLLEGE SHOGHORE CHITRAL

F.SC. PRE-ENGINEERING, 2011-2013

CERTIFICATION

CLOUD COMPUTING

Hazza Institute of Technology, Islamabad

CERTIFIED KUBERNETES ADMINISTRATOR (CKA)

• VIEW MY VERIFIED ACHIEVEMENT FROM THE LINUX FOUNDATION. HTTPS://WWW.CREDLY.COM/BADGES/04FAFFAE-4572-4CCD-85EE-7978FEE75FE8/LINKED_IN

Cloud Native Computing Foundation

PORTFOLIO LINK:

https://mehrab-uddin.netlify.app/